radar.net 2009-12-14

# Privacy Policy | Radar

## Company Privacy Policy

Tiny Pictures, Inc. (“Company”) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By accessing the Radar service, Radar.net and other Company websites, and any subscription-based features, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Statement.

## What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers Company's treatment of personal information that Company gathers when you are on the Company website and when you use Company services, including subscription-based features.

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Company does not own or control, or to individuals that Company does not employ or manage.

## What Personal Information About Customers Does Company Collect?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a personalized, useful, and efficient experience. We collect the following types of information from our customers:

### Information You Provide to Us:

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The personal information you provide is used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain products and services, customizing the content you see, and communicating with you about your account and your use of the services we provide.

### Registration:

In order for you to use the Radar service, you must complete a registration process. We require your contact information (such as name and email address). We may also request demographic information and unique identifiers in order to provide you with a more personalized service, as well as to comply with government requirements, such as those included in the United States Children's Online Privacy Act.

### Automatic Information:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via our website. Company automatically receives and records certain "traffic data" on our server logs including your IP address, Company cookie information, the page you requested, and your communications and interactions with other site registrants. Company uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze general activity trends and administer the service.

The Company service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and use of the service components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. This data is only used in the aggregate. This type of collective data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the service, so we can make the service appealing to as many customers as possible. In addition, we may provide statistical information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our service. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their areas and our service, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal experience.

We also collect and use information for internal purposes. For example, if you are a registered user of the Company's subscription-based services, we may keep records in your account history of complaints about other registered users' online behavior, and any reported violation of our Terms of Use that you or someone on your account may have committed.

### E-mail Communications:

We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from Company if your computer supports this type of program, in order to help us make e-mails more interesting and helpful. We may also send out emails with news or promotions. If you are a registered user of the Company's subscription-based services and do not want to receive e-mail from us, please follow the link provided at the bottom of each of these emails, or visit the settings options of our services to disable these emails.

### Information From Other Sources:

For purposes such as improving personalization of our service, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

## What about Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. Company cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your account name or email address is.

The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of Company's most attractive features.

## Will Company Share Any of the Information it Receives?

Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only with the entities that are controlled by or control Company and as described below.

### Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control:

We are affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, Company provides services, or sells products jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share customer information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business.

### Agents:

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples may include fulfilling orders, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. We may also provide your personal information to agents who will use it to verify aggregate usage data that we provide to our partners.

### Promotional Offers:

We may send offers to certain customers on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you are a registered user of the Company's subscription-based services and do not wish to receive these offers, please visit the settings options of our services to disable these offers.

### Business Transfers:

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets or businesses. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Company, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, customer information would be one of the assets that are transferred.

### Protection of Company and Others:

We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### With Your Consent:

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties.

## Is Information About Me Secure?

Your Company Account Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by signing off once you have finished using a shared computer.

Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.

## What Information Can I Access?

You can access your personal information on our site and correct, amend, or delete information that is inaccurate.

## What Choices Do I Have?

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to make a purchase or take advantage of certain Company features.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the “What Information Do I Have” section above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

If you are a registered user of Company's subscription-based services and do not wish to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please make sure you have disabled this option in your user account settings. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Company web site, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

As explained earlier, the “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if you do not enable cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features.

Our site and the services available through Company are not intended for children under the age of 13. Company does not knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 13 and believes that children of any age should get their parents' consent before giving out any personal information. We encourage you to participate in your child's web experience. Company recommends that parents use Web filtering technology to supervise their kids' access to the Web.

If you decide to visit Company site, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of United States law.

The service may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Company site. These other websites are not under Company control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by Company of those other websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Company site are not covered by this Privacy Statement, and Company is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

Company may amend this Privacy Policy. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will notify you by email or within Company's services so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at Company site, please contact us at [feedback@radar.net](mailto:feedback@radar.net) or by phone at 1-415-513-5998. Your privacy is important to us and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
